A Finding Aid to the Christine Burgin Gallery Records, 1980-2016, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Christine Burgin Gallery records
1980-2016
Archives of American Art
Christine Burgin Gallery
AAA.chriburg
Archival Resource Key
18 Linear feet
52.28 Gigabytes
The records of Christine Burgin Gallery, a New York City gallery representing conceptual artists from the United States and Europe, measure 18 linear feet and 52.28 GB, and date from 1980-2016. The collection documents the gallery's activities, projects, and relationships with artists through administrative files and business records, artist files, exhibition files, and client files. Artist files comprise nearly half of the collection and contain correspondence with artists and project files for numerous publications and editions the gallery produced in collaboration with artists. Some material is in born-digital form, including images of artwork and installations, slide shows, document files, as well as audiovisual recordings. The collection also contains two analog video recordings. Files dating from after the gallery's closure include additional correspondence, invoices, and project files.
Biographical / Historical
The Christine Burgin Gallery (established 1986; closed 2007), owned and operated by Christine Burgin, was a gallery in New York City that represented conceptual artists from the United States and Europe. The gallery operated from 1986-1992 and from 1999-2007. Gallery artists included Zoe Beloff, Victor Burgin, Ian Hamilton Finlay, Harrell Fletcher, Rodney Graham, Fariba Hajamadi, Paul Lincoln, Max Neuhaus, Richard Nonas, Hermann Pitz, Allen Ruppersberg, Victoria Sambunaris, Alan Saret, Jeanne Silverthorne, Michael Smith, and many others. In addition to staging solo and group exhibitions, the gallery produced numerous publications and editions in collaboration with artists.
Christine Burgin continues to publish books with her imprint at New Directions.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. Access to original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center.
Researchers interested in accessing born-digital records or audiovisual recordings in this collection must use access copies. Contact References Services for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated to the Archives of American Art in 2017 by Christine Burgin.
Scope and Contents
The records of Christine Burgin Gallery, a New York City gallery representing conceptual artists from the United States and Europe, measure 18 linear feet and 52.28 GB, and date from 1980-2016. The collection documents the gallery's activities, projects, and relationships with artists through administrative files and business records, artist files, exhibition files, and client files. Administrative files and business records document the operations and daily activities of the gallery. Artist files comprise nearly half of the collection and contain correspondence with artists, consignment and loan forms for exhibitions at other venues, inventories and sales invoices, photographic material, exhibitions announcements and catalogs, clippings, research and source material, as well as project files for numerous publications and editions the gallery produced in collaboration with artists. Exhibition files document the dozens of exhibitions at the gallery during their two periods of operation, 1986-1992 and 1999-2007, and include correspondence, price lists, installation documentation, photographic material, press releases, artist biographies, exhibition announcements, and clippings. Client files predominantly contain correspondence and invoices to clients. Some material is in born-digital form, including images of artwork and installations, slide shows, document files, as well as audiovisual recordings. The collection also contains two analog video recordings.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as four series
Series 1: Administrative Files and Business Records, 1985-2012 (1.1 linear feet; Boxes 1-2)
Series 2: Artist Files, 1980-2016 (8.4 linear feet, Boxes 2-10; 35.75 GB, ER01-ER29)
Series 3: Exhibition Files, 1986-2015 (5 linear feet, Boxes 10-15; 16.53 GB, ER30-ER43)
Series 4: Client Files, 1983-2013 (3.5 linear feet; Boxes 15-18)
Art galleries, Commercial -- New York (State); Burgin, Christine; Finlay, Ian Hamilton; Smith, Michael; Graham, Rodney, 1949-; Ruppersberg, Allen, 1944-
- Administrative Files and Business Records, 1985-2012; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 1.1 Linear feet Boxes 1-2
  Scope and Contents
  Administrative files and business records date from 1985-2012 and document the daily activities of the gallery. Files pertain to art fairs, consignments, gallery purchases and sales, and other routine operations.
  - Art Fairs, Archival Resource Key (Box 1)
    - Applications and Invitations, 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Armory Show, 2000-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
    - Art Basel Miami Beach, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
    - Artissma, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Notebook, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Consignments, 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Consignments, 2000-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Expenses, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Floor Plan, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Incomplete Projects and Research, 1991-2004; 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
  - Mailing Lists, 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Purchases, Inventory, 1985-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sales Invoices, 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Sales Invoices, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sales Invoices, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Artist Files, 1980-2016; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 8.4 Linear feet Boxes 2-10; 35.75 Gigabytes ER01-ER29
  Artist files date from 1980-2016 and comprise nearly half of the collection at 8.4 linear feet and 35.75 GB. Files contain correspondence with artists, consignment and loan forms for exhibitions at other venues, inventories and sales invoices, photographic material, exhibitions announcements and catalogs, clippings, research and source material, as well as project files for numerous publications and editions the gallery produced in collaboration with artists. This series contains material in born-digital form, including images of artwork and installations, document files, as well as audiovisual recordings. Also found here are two analog video recordings of Gert Verhoeven's film, The Blob. Files pertaining to exhibitions at Christine Burgin Gallery are arranged in series 3.
  - Bain, Mark, 1997-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Barthelme, Frederick, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Beloff, Zoe, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - The Coney Island Amateur Psychoanalytic Society and Its Circle Book Project, 2008-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER01
    - The Coney Island Amateur Psychoanalytic Society and Its Circle, Book Jacket Image, 2009; Archival Resource Key; 0.225 Gigabytes 2 computer files (Folder ER01)
    - Correspondence, 2008-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER02
    - Correspondence, Effulgence of the North Digital Video Recording from The Velaslavasay Panorama, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.278 Gigabytes 1 computer file (Folder ER02)
    - Magic Show Traveling Exhibition, 2009-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER03
    - Magic Show Installation Images, 2009-2011; Archival Resource Key; 0.084 Gigabytes 42 computer files (Folder ER03)
    - Printed Material, 2008-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Published Projects, 1996; 2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 videodisc (DVD) and the digital artwork "Beyond" on CD (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Research and Source Material, 2005-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER04
    - Research and Source Material, Images and Video Recordings, 2005-2010; Archival Resource Key; 4.79 Gigabytes 30 computer files (Folder ER04)
    - The Somnambulists: A Compendium of Source Material Book Project, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER05
    - The Somnambulists Drafts and Images, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.147 Gigabytes 4 computer files (Folder ER05)
    - Still Images from Video Installation, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Blaine, Dominique, 1994-1995; 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bloom, Barbara, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Braine, Bob, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Brouwn, Stanley, 2006-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Buk, Eli, 2001-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Includes born-digital file, see ER06
  - Buk, Eli, Digital Video Recording, 2013; Archival Resource Key; 1.29 Gigabytes 1 computer file (Folder ER06)
  - Bullock, Leonard, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Burden, Chris, 1987-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Burgin, Victor, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - Appraisals, 2004-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Consignments and Loans, 2001-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER07
    - Consignments and Loans, Digital Images, 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.246 Gigabytes 4 computer files (Folder ER07)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Fundació Antoni Tàpies, 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Inventories, 1999-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Oakland Museum, 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Printed Material, 2000-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER08
    - Printed Material, Digital Images of Artwork Shadowed, 2000; Archival Resource Key; 0.473 Gigabytes 99 computer files (Folder ER08)
  - Calle, Sophie, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Caramelle, Ernst, 1986-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Closky, Claude, 1999-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - de Cordier, Thierry and Louis, 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Corillon, Patrick, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Deutsch, David, 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Dion, Mark, 1984-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dorner, Helmut, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Dujourie, Lili, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Finlay, Ian Hamilton, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - Consignments and Loans, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - French Revolution Controversy, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - The Garden on the Hill Monograph Draft, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - The Garden on the Hill Monograph Requests, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Printed Material, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Proposal for Garden, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Fletcher, Harrell, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - Consignments, 2005-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Includes born-digital file, see ER09
    - Correspondence, Digital Image, 2004; Archival Resource Key; 0.005 Gigabytes 1 computer file (Folder ER09)
    - Printed Material, 1999-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Fontana, Bill, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER10
  - Fontana, Bill, Digital Audio Files, "Sounds from Sculpture", 2002; Archival Resource Key; 0.69 Gigabytes 9 computer files (Folder ER10)
  - Geys, Jef, 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Graham, Dan, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Graham, Rodney, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - Artwork Index Cards, 1988-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Biographical Material, 1991-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Book List, 1998-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - British Weathervanes Publication, 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER11
    - British Weathervanes, Digital Images, 2009; Archival Resource Key; 0.458 Gigabytes 12 computer files (Folder ER11)
    - Can of Worms Lightbox Edition, 2000-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Consignments and Loans, 1981-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Consignments and Loans, 1999-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1988-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
    - Dr. No Publication, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Essence of Smoke Lightbox Edition, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
    - Freud Supplement (170A-170D) Catalog, 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - A Glass of Beer Edition, 2005-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER12
    - A Glass of Beer, Digital Image, 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.296 Gigabytes 1 computer file (Folder ER12)
    - Graham: Peinture Catalog, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Invoices, 1987-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Mariachi Bowtie Prints, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Nautical Scene with Loudhailer Edition, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Photographic Material, 1990-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER13
    - Photographic Material, Digital Images, 2004; Archival Resource Key; 0.018 Gigabytes 18 computer files (Folder ER13)
    - Piano Stool Lightbox Edition, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Ponderosa Pines Edition, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Printed Material, Articles and Verwandlungsmusik Audio CD, 1991-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 sound disc (CD) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Printed Material, Exhibition Announcements, 1988-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Printed Material, Press, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Projects, Assorted, 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Research and Source Material, 1988-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Sales Records, 1987-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Tattoo Project, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Includes born-digital file, see ER14
    - Tattoo Project, Digital Image, Archival Resource Key; 0.093 Gigabytes 1 computer file (Folder ER14)
    - Typewriter with Flour Lightbox Edition, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - White Shirt, Barneys Installation, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Godfrey, Dewitt, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hajamadi, Fariba, Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
    - Biographical Material, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Consignments and Loans, 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
    - Correspondence, 1987-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
    - Photographic Material, 1985-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Printed Material, Exhibition Announcements, 1987-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Printed Material, Exhibition Catalogs, 1988-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Printed Material, Press, 1987-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Sales Records, 1987-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Horndash, Ulrich, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Hyde, James, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Iglesias, Cristina, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Jay, Ricky, Matthias Buchinger: The Greatest German Living Book Project, 2007; 2015-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER15
  - Jay, Ricky, Book Project Digital Images, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.579 Gigabytes 46 computer files (Folder ER15)
  - Jonas, Joan, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kelley, Mike, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Klingelhöller, Harald, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Kwiatek, Greg, 1995-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln, Paul, Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - Biographical Material, 1991-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Consignments and Loans, 1991-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER16
    - Consignments and Loans, Digital Images, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.562 Gigabytes 15 computer files (Folder ER16)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - The Glover's Repository Publication, 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Photographic Material, 1990-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER17
    - Photographic Material, Digital Images, 2007-2012; Archival Resource Key; 0.307 Gigabytes 32 computer files (Folder ER17)
    - Print Editions, 2002-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Printed Material, 1991-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Project Proposals, 1999-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Sales Records, 1991; 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Sinfonia Torinese Publication, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER18
    - Sinfonia Torinese, Digital Image, 2004; Archival Resource Key; 0.053 Gigabytes 1 computer file (Folder ER18)
    - A Violet Somnambulist Spiriting the Fugacious Bloom Publication, 1997-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - McCollum, Allan, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Meyer, Jürgen, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Middlebrook, Tom, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Mullican, Matt, 2006-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER19
  - Mullican, Matt, Digital Images and Document, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes 7 computer files (Folder ER19)
  - Murphy, John, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Nauman, Bruce, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Nelson, David, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Neuhaus, Max, Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Inventory and Shipping Records, 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Lecture at San Francisco Art Institute, Digital Video Recording, 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.347 Gigabytes 1 computer file (Folder ER20)
    - Notes for Profile of Neuhaus, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Press Package, 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Times Square Reinstallation, Budget, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Times Square Reinstallation, Correspondence, 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Times Square Reinstallation, Correspondence, 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Times Square Reinstallation, Dia Art Foundation, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Times Square Reinstallation, Documentary Video, 2002; Archival Resource Key; 4.21 Gigabytes 1 computer file (Folder ER21)
    - Times Square Reinstallation, Logistics, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Times Square Reinstallation, Press Package, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Times Square Reinstallation, Proposal, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Nonas, Richard, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - Ace Gallery, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Press Packet, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Nordman, Maria, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Othoniel, Jean-Michel, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Pitz, Hermann, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - Consignments, 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1987-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Printed Material, 1986-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Potter, Tina, circa 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Puett, Morgan, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ruppersberg, Allen, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - Benefits, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Biography and Resumes, circa 1992-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Consignments and Loans, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20-23)
    - Consignments and Loans, 2000s-2010s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence, 2000s-2010s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Essay by Allan McCollum, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Fishing is Fun Puzzle Edition, 2003-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Grey Flags (2006), Exhibition at Sculpture Center, Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 CD (transfer not possible) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Inventories and Price Lists, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - No Time Left to Start Again Edition, Slide Show and Audio Files, 1994; 2012; Archival Resource Key; 2.17 Gigabytes 17 computer files (Folder ER22)
    - Photographic Material, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Printed Material, Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Projects, Various, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Remainders Edition, 1991-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Sales Records and Expenses, 1990s-2010s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ruscha, Ed, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sambunaris, Victoria, Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Invoices and Receipts, 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Printed Material, 2000-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Sales Records, 2001-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Saret, Alan, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - 7 Objects Artwork Multiple, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Biography, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Consignments and Loans, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)